Renz Ferbi A Comiso

CONTACT

31020 9th Ave S Federal Way, WA 98003

rnzfrb@gmail.com (408) 904-8990

OBJECTIVE

To obtain a position where I can gain more experience and seek a full-time career to utilize my skills and experience with computers and all sorts of technology, equipment and machine.

EDUCATION

BS Information Technology

2010 - 2014

Lyceum of the Philippines University - Cavite

High School 2006 — 2010

Colegio de San Francisco

WORK EXPERIENCE

Dataknox Solutions, Inc.

December 2020 — February 2021

IT Repair Technician

- Installing software/OS
- Troubleshooting and/or repair of electronic device
- Reconfiguring electronic devices to factory default
- Reconfiguring network switches to factury default
- Determining if an electronic device scrap, needs repair or for resale
- Wiping hard drives
- Assess warehouse inventory using RazorERP

Micropoint Bioscience Inc.

April 2019 — May 2020

Engineering Technician

- Troubleshooting and/or repair of various machine and equipment
- Setting up various machine
- Calibrating peristaltic pump
- Programming/Editing of the alignment of Fisnar Robot Arm
- Doing daily, weekly and annual preventive maintenance
- Review and update of engineering inventory

Micropoint Bioscience Inc.

March 2018 — April 2019

Manufacturing Operator

- Operates various factory machines such as
 - Ultra Sonic Cleaner Machine
 - Jet Dryer
 - Wetbench
 - Automated Dispensing Machine
 - Manual Dispensing Machine

Renz Ferbi A Comiso

Naval Research and Technology Development Center - Philippine Navy

IT Officer II

- Conducted troubleshooting for various computer equipment at the office
- Provided day to day support of client desktop, laptops, printers, networks, and servers.
- Installation new software that is needed by the office
- Assembling and disassembling of system units
- Monitored the office's firewall
- Troubleshoot and resolve network and system issues.
- Assisted on managing active directory
- Setting up Audio/Visual equipment
- Organized and archived confidential office files
- Create/edit slide presentations
- Edit photos and videos for various projects
- Create design such as logos, backdrop, and certificates & awards
- Assisted with preparations for various international events representing the Philippine Navy
- Assisted with magazine layout
- Assisted on various research paper

Naval Research and Technology Development Center - Philippine Navy

October 2014 — December 2014

Admin Officer - Intern

- Conducted troubleshooting for various computer equipment at the office
- Create/edit slide presentations
- Organized and archived confidential office files
- Assisted on managing Active Directory
- Assisted on various research paper

CERTIFICATES

- 10th Philippines Youth Congress on Information Technology University of the Philippines
- Project Management Seminar
- Workshop on Cyber Defense and Security and Radars and Electronic Warfare Research and Development
- Seminar on Increasing Productivity through Value Based Time
- Naval Defense Technology Management Seminar

SKILLS

Microsoft Office: MS Word, MS Excel, MS Powerpoint, MS Access

iWork: Pages, Numbers, Keynote

Operating System Proficiency/Familiarity: Windows, MacOS

PC Hardware: PC building, PC/Laptop repair and/or troubleshooting

Photography/Videography

Photo Editing: Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Lightroom

Video Editing: Final Cut Pro, Adobe Premiere

Layout: Adobe InDesign

Programming: HTML5, CSS, PHP, Java, MySQL

Languages: English, Filipino

Renz Ferbi A Comiso 2

PROFILE

I finish tasks and projects assigned to me immediately. I'm a fast learner as long as it is explained proficiently. I am able to solve problems through study and research. When communicating with people, I am straightforward, but I also play well with others, as this was a vital step for my previous positions. Art takes up a big part of my life, whether I'm creating it or consuming it.

Renz Ferbi A Comiso 3